♪Beneath the mask♪
♪Lies another mask♪
(Original Story: Haishi Lisheng)
♪Who's sincere♪
♪Who's only pretending♪
♪Borrowing your light♪
♪I walk through my own night♪
♪You are my weakness♪
♪And my weapon too♪
♪Draped in your shadow♪
♪I walk the blade's edge♪
♪If one day♪
♪The mask shatters♪
♪Will you still♪
♪Recognize my light♪
=The Masked Lover=
I can't believe you actually scored 100.
You trusted me, Adjutant He,
and gave me such an important job.
Of course I couldn't let you down.
But what you did today was too risky.
Don't do it again.
Don't you dare run.
Come back.
What?
You won't let me touch her.
Can't I touch someone else?
Get inside.
I need to talk to you.
Are you okay?
=Episode 6=
Here.
How could he do this to you?
He's not human.
He's not even a man.
He can't even perform.
He's a monster.
(I'm only warning you
for your own good.)
(If you truly knew)
(what kind of man he is,)
(you'd never entertain that idea again.)
(So...)
(he really was warning me
for my own good.)
Ms. Lu.
Can you save me?
You know perfectly well
I'm not really Ms. Lu.
We're the same.
We're not.
They gave up on me.
You're carrying out the mission now.
So you know what they're after?
They gave up on me
before they ever told me.
Meanwhile,
Lu Shaoyun took an interest in me.
My grandfather needed treatment.
I had no choice.
I thought if I stayed with him,
it'd be worth it
if he paid Grandpa's medical bills.
How could...
How could I know he'd be a monster?
He enjoys tormenting people.
If this keeps up,
sooner or later, they'll kill me.
Ms. Lu.
Please.
Please save me.
Give me some time.
I'll arrange something.
Until then,
you'll have to hang on.
Don't tip them off.
Okay.
(Guanghe Theater)
I heard you've taken in new students.
(1,000 taels)
Use this however you need.
This...
Tell me if it's not enough.
This... this...
You're very kind, Ms. Lu.
By the way,
I found the person you asked about.
She's at a small inn by the station.
Here are the tickets you asked for.
(Railway Bureau Special Express
Fancheng-Nancheng, 2nd Class)
Thank you, Troupe Master.
You're welcome.
Are you sure you weren't mistaken?
Absolutely.
It was identical to the mark
on Ms. Lu's shoulder.
Looks like they have more than one pawn.
Lili.
Here.
There's money and a ticket inside.
It's enough for
your grandpa's treatment.
The train leaves in two hours.
Your grandpa's waiting at the station.
Go.
Be careful.
(Railway Bureau Special Express
Fancheng-Nancheng, 2nd Class)
Go to the station.
Bring her grandfather here too.
Yes.
Lady Feng, spare me!
Please let my grandfather go.
Please!
That depends on how well you perform
in front of the governor.
Ms. Lu.
You can't keep practicing shooting
like this.
You'll ruin your hand.
I know.
Thank you, Doctor.
I'll be going.
Weren't you yesterday's rickshaw driver?
What happened to you?
It's you,
miss.
Last night was a disaster.
You asked me to take that girl
to the station.
We were halfway there
when two men and a woman ambushed us.
They dragged the girl away.
And this is what they did to me.
Do you remember what they looked like?
I didn't know the men,
but I'd given that woman a ride before.
I think she was
a maid to one of the concubines
at your residence.
(Are you looking to buy it?)
(Yanyan.)
(Give me a son,)
(and I'll make you my principal wife.)
(Looks like there are more of us
in this together than I thought.)
(They gave up on me.)
(You're carrying out the mission now.)
(If Feng Yanyan is one of them too,)
(why is she so determined to expose me?)
(Whatever the reason,)
(she's trying to expose my identity.)
(I can simply tell He Jingchen)
(and let him handle her.)
Miss.
Here.
For your medical bills.
Take care.
Thank you, miss.
Why didn't you do as I said that day?
I told you I needed a child.
But you don't have one.
Then give me one.
I knew it all along.
You're determined to
establish her as Lu Zhentian's daughter.
If she really is his daughter,
marry her and you'll be
the Lu family's true son-in-law.
You'd have a more legitimate claim
than Lu Shaoyun, the fake son.
A claim to what?
The Lu family's chamber of commerce.
Control of the Lu Army.
Don't deny it.
(Soon everyone will know)
(there's no real Ms. Lu.)
(I won't let you marry
into the Lu family.)
(Feng Yanyan is out to get me.)
(He Jingchen can't seem to bring himself
to be ruthless with her.)
(But a fake is still a fake.)
(If I'm bound to be exposed someday,)
(instead of worrying every day,)
(I should turn the tables.)
(If Lu Zhentian learns
I'm not really his daughter)
(and still accepts me,)
(then the photo He Jingchen has)
(will become worthless.)
(I won't have to be so wary of him.)
Looks like
I should thank Lady Feng
for handing me this opportunity.
Yutang, you're here.
Father.
Father, get some rest.
Let me tell you a story.
What story?
Father, remember the painting
Lady Feng gave you on your birthday?
I do.
The one with two monkeys and the Buddha.
Actually,
there's another version of that story.
Legend says the Buddha knew
the Six-Eared Macaque was an impostor,
but chose not to expose him.
Instead, he let him keep protecting
Tang Sanzang on his journey west.
Move.
Let go of me!
Rickshaw!
Where to?
Governor's Residence.
Right away.
Lady Feng.
They're here.
Governor.
Lady Feng wants you
in the front courtyard.
Please see Lu Shaoyun for who he is
and avenge your own daughter.
I'll get to the bottom of this.
♪A lie carved deep into the heart♪
(Loyalty Eternal)
♪Blades clash, leaving us both trapped♪
♪Nightmares from days gone by♪
♪Love and hate intertwine♪
♪In eyes ignited by sparks♪
♪Each blooming with a fierce edge♪
♪Shattering moonlight on the ground♪
♪I look up and meet your gaze♪
♪Unveiling all the absurdity♪
♪Seeking love's only truth♪
♪Through fate's layered maze♪
♪Charging toward the unknown♪
♪Don't forget your stubborn heart♪
♪Fire tempers the strength to go on♪
♪Counting down the long night's haze♪
♪With my own hands, I draw the dawn♪
♪Boundless♪